

DEVI JAGANNADH

CYBER SECURITY ENTHUSIASTIC

CONTACT

Phone: 8179376372

Email: devijagannadh@gmail.com

Web: www.thedj.tech

PROFILE

I am a vibrant individual who love to explore the magnificent subject cybersecurity. Every day, I try to explore new things in Networking world, I was proud white hat hacker who protects world against hackers and cyber attacks. Making an impact in the world through my works has been my passion and now I want to take the lead to ace in it.

PROJECTS

- Wifi snooping system using arduino .
 Mar 2018 Oct 2018
- Fingerprint Door Unlocking System.
 Mar 2019 Jun 2019
- Gesture controlled car using arduino.
 Jul 2019 Oct 2019
- Online quiz portal using Php Jul 2021 Jan 2021

SKILLS

- Ethical hacking
- Web application pen testing
- Network security
- Bash scripting and automation
- Cloud computing
- Secure coding
- Software development
- Network programming
- SQL and NoSQL database management
- Defensive and offensive tools
- Malware Development (Ethical)
- Cryptography
- Python
- Java
- Researching
- Web development

WORK EXPERIENCE

Red Team Pen Tester

FRESH DIGITAL CONSULTING SERVICES NOV 2020 - DEC 2020

- Web Research
- Detecting Bugs
- Exploiting Vulnerabilities
- Reporting

Vice President

NULL (INFOSEC) CHAPTER - VIT AP OCT 2020 - PRESENT

- Departments management
- Working on technical projects
- Conducting events
- Strategizing
- Collaborations and partnerships

Intern

VIRTUALLY TESTING FOUNDATION JAN 2021 - FEB 2021

- Virtualization
- Hands on experience
- Experimenting

EDUCATION

B.Tech Computer Science Engineering Sp. in Networking and Security

VELLORE INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, AP 2018 - 2022 CGPA: 8.6

Intermediate - MPC

NARAYANA JUNIOR COLLEGE JUL 2016 - APR 2018 CGPA: 9.41

10 th Grade - CBSE

KAVIRAYANI PUBLIC SCHOOL JUN 2015 - JUN 2016 CGPA: 8.0